Why not?
Why not? Maybe--maybe she's right. You know, maybe I should have put it in the paper, maybe I should have done something different
The thing is, if you just do stuff and nothing happens
What's it all mean? what's the point?
Oh right, this this whole thing is about self-acceptance
Kicking the hell out of yourself doesn't give meaning to anything
So I should stop?
judging
and accept to start
So no matter what I do
Hurray for me because I'm a great guy? It's all good?
No matter how many dogs I kill I just, what, do an inventory and accept
I mean you backed your truck over your own kid, and you like accept?
What a load of crap.
Hey, Jessie, I know you're in pain--
No, y-you know what?
Why I'm here in the first place
Is to sell you meth
You're nothing to me, but customers!
I made you my bitch! You okay with that? Huh? You accept?
No.
About time.
Jesse! Stop what you're doing, turn and face me!
You wanna--you wanna know what he did?
You wanna hear about it?
Jesse! Put out the lighter.
He poisoned a little kid
An eight year old boy just because, you know, just as a move!
Now Walt's a bastard.
Secret's out, we'll talk about it. I need you to put out the lighter
Jesse--
See I don't wanna kill you, and you don't want to be killed.
So put it out.
He can't keep getting away with it!
You wanna burn him down?
Let's do it together.
Back off!
You stay where you are what I don't know what happened here what I do.
You stole it off from me
You and him just took it right out of my pocket
Calm down. Yes, okay. I had him lift your dope, I couldn't risk the gun out take it you No! Before
the cigarettes you stole
cigarette what the ricin cigarette
You and him stole it off me.. and over here that Mr. White
He poisoned Brock! You poison Brock to you
You helped him, okay, Jesse?
Calm down. Say it again
Tell me one more time to calm down, come on. I'm sorry just
Yes, okay, I heard he will lift your cigarette. What maybe he told me he was helping you. He was saving you
I never would have a great time. I know what he was gonna do
God believe me. I didn't wanna any of this
Back up
You're turning down one and a half
Million dollars, I'm not turning down the money. I'm turning down
you
You get it I?
I don't want nothing to do with you
Ever since I met you everything I've ever cared about
It's gone
Ruined , turned to shit, dead ever since I hooked up with the great Heisenberg
Have never been more alone
I have nothing, no one
All right, it's all gone get it?
No no no why
Why would you
Get it. What do you even care as long as you get what's you want?
right you
Don't give a shit about me
You said I was no good
I'm nothing
Why would you want me, huh?
You said my meth
is inferior
right
Right hey you said my cook. What's garbage?
Its screw you man
screw you
How about you that I will want to use a beer you have any
Jesse?
I almost shot you hey hey, no, I almost killed you all because
listen
You've just misunderstanding. No-no-no-no
No, it's only there's no way anything I
Why don't I get visas, stupid
You just get to stop it now, come on, come on. Come on
I'm so sorry
It's Okay
Listen me
What happened happened for the best, do you hear me
I wouldn't change it you and I working together
Having each other's back
It's what saved our lives
I want you to think about that as we go forward
Go forward where
Do it
You want this
Sill words!
Say you want this
Nothing happens until I hear you say it
I want this
And do-it-yourself
Um take what every one of them I have money
I got whole amount of money
Don't do this
You heard  you
You don't have to do this