[ Hit Man ]
We happy?
Vincent?
- We happy?
- Yeah, we happy.
[ Sighs ]
[ Brett ] Look, I'm sorry, uh, l--
I didn't get your name.
I got yours. Vincent. Right?
B-But I never got yours.
- My name's Pitt, and your ass
ain't talkin' your way outta this shit.
- No, no, no.
I just want you
to know how--
I just want you to know how sorry we are
th-that things got so fucked up...
with us and Mr. Wallace.
W-We got into this thing with
the best intentions. Really. I never--
Oh, I'm sorry,
did I break your concentration?
- [ Gasping ]
- I didn't mean to do that. Please.
Continue. You were saying something
about "best intentions."
What's the matter?
Oh, you were finished!
Oh, well, allow me to retort.
What does Marsellus Wallace
look like?
What?
- What country you from?
- What?
- "What" ain't no country I ever
heard of. They speak English in What?
- W-What?
- English, motherfucker!
Do you speak it?
- Yes!
- Then you know what I'm sayin'!
- Yes.
Describe what Marsellus Wallace
looks like!
- What? l--
- Say "what" again!
Say "what" again! I dare ya!
I double dare you, motherfucker!
- Say "what" one more goddamn time!
- H-H-He's black.
- Go on!
- He's bald!
- Does he look like a bitch?
- What?
- [ Gunshot ]
- [ Screaming ]
Does he look... Iike a bitch?
- No!
- Then why you tryin'
to fuck him like a bitch?
- I didn't.
- Yes, you did. Yes, you did, Brett!
- You tried to fuck him.
- [ Gasping ] No, no.
But Marsellus Wallace don't like to be
fucked by anybody except Mrs. Wallace.
- You read the Bible, Brett?
- Yes!
Well, there's this passage
I got memorized. Sort of
fits this occasion.
Ezekiel 25:17.
"The path of the righteous man...
is beset on all sides
by the inequities of the selfish...
and the tyranny of evil men.
Blessed is he who,
in the name of charity and goodwill,
shepherds the weak
through the valley of darkness,
for he is truly
his brother's keeper...
and the finder
of lost children.
And I will strike down upon thee
with great vengeance...
and furious anger...
those who attempt to poison
and destroy My brothers!
And you will know
My name is the Lord...
when I lay My vengeance
upon thee!"